Contact

2485613963 (Mobile) darlene.douglas26@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/darlenedouglas-ms-crna-802307b1 (LinkedIn) yahoo.com (Personal)

Top Skills

Hospitals Social Networking Strategic Planning

Darlene Douglas MS., CRNA

Nurse Anesthetist

Troy

Summary

Full time Independant contractor ~ DMD Anesthesia Services Inc., primarily working at UnaSource Surgery Center located in Troy, Mi. Manages daily CRNA assignments, orientation and problem solving, lead CRNA. Specializing in Pediatric and orthopedic anesthesia. Served as Chair of St. Anastasia Catholic Church Council at large, located in Troy Mi. In 2016. Still active member in the church.

Experience

Dado Publishing LLC

Owner

November 2014 - Present (5 years 10 months)

Former owner/publisher of MY magazine (Southern Oakland County)

November 2014 - April 2015

Nurse Anesthetist

CRNA

December 1997 - Present (22 years 9 months)

Troy, Michigan

Work as a Nurse Anesthetist. Employed by (ASC) Anesthesia Staffing Consultants Inc., full service anesthesia management company.

Education

University of Detroit Mercy

Master of Science (MS), Nurse Anesthetist · (1995 - 1997)